costhelper.com 2019-01-03

# Privacy Policy

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

This policy covers how CostHelper.com treats personal information that CostHelper.com collects and receives, including information related to your past use of CostHelper.com products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that CostHelper.com does not own or control, or to people that CostHelper.com does not employ or manage. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

CostHelper.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except under the following circumstances: 

a)       We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; 

b)       We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of CostHelper.com's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

c)       We transfer information about you if CostHelper.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, CostHelper.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

d)       CostHelper.com reserves the right to display targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, users interesting in a particular good or services from a particular geographic area. 

o      CostHelper.com does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. 

e)       CostHelper.com works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business. 

**Cookies**

CostHelper.com may set and access cookies on your computer. 

CostHelper.com reserves the right to let other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to CostHelper.com's cookies. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/pdfs/NAI_principles.pdf). 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

**Your Email Address**

We reserve the right to contact the email address you provide to verify your identity, and to notify you of information related to your post or inquiry.  If you send us a question, comment or any kind of feedback, we reserve the right to contact you.  We reserve the right to periodically notify previous posters of responses or updates regarding their post, or about enhancements to our site that may interest them. 

**Confidentiality and Security**

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. . 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

CostHelper.com may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your CostHelper.com post or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

**Questions and Suggestions**

If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us at: 

CostHelper.com Inc.  
PO Box 111450  
Campbell, CA 95011
